Guide to the Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay Records SC1247
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay, records
1921-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay
SC1247
3.25 Linear Feet 3 boxes
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of minutes, reports, program materials, directories, clippings, photographs, and audio/video recordings relating to the Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay.
Organizational History
The Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay, founded in 1921, organizes a wide range of intellectual, cultural and professional offerings and opportunities to interact with alumnae and female family members of past and current Stanford students in Alameda and Contra Costa counties.
Related Collection
Stanford Women's Club records (SC0491)
clippings (information artifacts); Stanford alumni; Minutes.; Women -- Social networks.; Stanford University; Women -- California -- Societies and clubs; Women -- California.; Stanford Women's Club of the East Bay
- Records, 1921-2015 (Item 1-2)
  - Minutes and reports, 1921-2013; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) Includes 1 optical disc (CD) containing minutes, 2005-2008. (Box 2, Box 1)
  - Directories, 1979-2013 (Box 1)
  - Program materials, 1957-2000 (Box 1)
  - Program materials, 1983-2011 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1937-1962 (Box 2)
  - Photographs, 2008; 14 computer file(s) (jpg)
  - Media, 2001-01-24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) One videotape (VHS) and one audiocassette relating to Books on Review, 2001. (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-058
  - Administrative records, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - Member Directories [incomplete run], 1992-2006 (Box 1)